econotimes.com 2015-11-08

# Breaking News, Business, Financial and Economic News, World News from EconoTimes

EconoTimes is a fast growing non-partisan source of news and intelligence on global economy and financial markets, providing timely, relevant, and critical insights for market professionals and those who want to make informed investment decisions.

Traditional news outlets can be reactive rather than proactive. Our core belief is that investors demand ideology-agnostic and "smart beta" news in a growing decentralized multi-speed world.

Our credibility for delivering insightful information has been built over last 5 years by a global network of analysts. Our reporters include former fixed-income and currency traders and experts, rather than sell-side analysts. Expert analysts convey the key market moving news and events in the shortest and most succinct format possible.

Please contact us at [info@econotimes.com](mailto:info@econotimes.com) for any news tips.

**EconoTimes PRO**

EconoTimes PRO is an exclusive platform for fundamental investors and buy-side professionals. It offers access to a newsfeed, economic calendar, charts with daily reports and top trading ideas. From a risk management point of view, users receive a 24 hour early access to key articles before they are released to our community of free subscribers. On average, 800-1,000 headlines and articles are published per day.

EconoTimes is the premier gateway for marketers and agencies to reach professional and retail investors worldwide.

EconoTimes is an independent source for news that tracks the fast-moving developments at the intersection of economy and alternative investing. EconoTimes provides real-time insight into the newest developments and latest trends in investing. 

EconoTimes reaches over 200,000 monthly unique visitors worldwide.

Please contact us at [info@econotimes.com](mailto:info@econotimes.com) for more opportunities.

The following Terms of service govern your use of this Website, and any content made available on this Website.

The information on this Website is for information purposes only. It is believed to be reliable, but EconoTimes does not warrant its completeness, timeliness or accuracy. The information on the Website is not intended as an offer or solicitation of any security or any financial instrument. The information and materials contained in this Website - and the terms and conditions of the access to and use of such information and materials - are subject to change without notice. Products and services described, as well as associated fees, charges, interest rates, and balance requirements may differ among geographic locations. Not all products and services are offered at all locations. 

You agree that:

(i) you will not engage in any activities related to the Website that are contrary to applicable law, regulation or the terms of any agreements you have with EconoTimes.

(ii) In any circumstances where locations of the Website require identification for access, you will establish commercially reasonable security procedures and controls to limit access to your password or other identifying information to authorized individuals. EconoTimes or its affiliates may discontinue or make changes in the information, products, or services described herein at any time without prior notice to you and without any liability to you. Any dated information is published as of its date only, and EconoTimes does not undertake any obligation or responsibility to update or amend any such information. EconoTimes reserves the right to terminate any or all Website information, offerings or transmissions without prior notice to the user. 

Furthermore, by offering this Website and information, products, or services via the Website, no distribution or solicitation is made by EconoTimes to any person to use the Website or such information, products, or services in jurisdictions where the provision of the Website and such information, products, services is prohibited by law. 

Any questions about this Terms of service should be addressed to [info@econotimes.com.](mailto:info@econotimes.com)

We are committed to protecting our customers' personal and financial information. In the course of providing you with financial products, information, and services, we need to collect and maintain certain nonpublic personal information about you. This Privacy Statement answers some questions about what nonpublic personal information we collect, what we do with it, and how we protect it. We do not sell your personal information to anyone.

We collect nonpublic information about you from the following sources:

\- Information we receive from you on applications or other forms.  
\- Information about your transactions with EconoTimes.

We do not disclose any nonpublic information about you or former customers to anyone other than affiliates, except as permitted or required by law. For example, this may include providing information to companies that perform support services on our behalf or to providing tax information to the IRS.

We restrict access to your nonpublic information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you.

We maintain a strict policy to maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect nonpublic personal information.

Should have any questions regarding your account, please contact the support team at [info@econotimes.com.](mailto:info@econotimes.com)

Trading in the futures and foreign exchange markets on margin carries a high level of risk, and may not be suitable for all individuals. The high degree of leverage offered in the Forex markets can work against you as well as for you. Before deciding to trade in the foreign exchange markets you should carefully consider your investment objectives, your level of experience, and your risk appetite.

The possibility exists that you could sustain a loss of some or all of your equity and therefore you should not invest money that you cannot afford to lose. Only true discretionary cash should be used in trading. You should make yourself aware of all the risks associated with foreign exchange trading and seek advice from an independent financial advisor if you have any questions or concerns as to how a loss would affect your lifestyle.

Any questions about this Disclaimer (Risk Warning) should be addressed to [info@econotimes.com.](mailto:info@econotimes.com)
